Caleb Wagner

Software Developer

calebwagner5@gmail.com • 615-636-7127 • calebwagner.github.io/portfolio-website/

CAREER SUMMARY

Experience 1+ year as Software Developer leading the Google Analytics 4 application upgrade

improving user experience and site analytic coverage by over 25%.

LanguagesJavascript, Python, Django, Java, SpringBoot, React, Ember, Vue, SQLToolsVisual Studio Code, GitHub, Git, PostMan, Swagger, Intellij, Azure DevOps

Methodologies Scrum, Kanban, CI/CD, Pair Programming

App Management Experience with foundational and platform upgrades

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HCA Healthcare - Digital Patient Experience

Nashville, TN

Application Engineer I

01/2022 - 08/2022

Technologies: Javascript, Java, SpringBoot, React, Vue, Ember, CSS, HTML, SQL Server, IBM DB2

- Part of a 7 person developer team enhancing and supporting product serving over 5 million users.
- Released features and bug fixes as part of 2-week sprints, with a personal velocity of 4 items per sprint.
- Responsible for upgrading 2 new features and maintaining 10+ others features, with 2 legacy.

Application Engineer Intern

10/2021 - 12/2021

- Paid internship turned into a permanent position.
- Enhanced and maintained static landing page for desktop and mobile desktop applications.
- Worked on tasks assigned by Sr. Team members such as bug fixes, issue resolution, and root cause analysis.

Projects

Where Was I | Front-End Application | Solo Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, JSX, CSS

- Built a productivity note-taking application as part of boot camp capstone.
- My goal for this application was to incorporate CRUD functionality and further my understanding of React.

uTeachiLearn | Full-Stack Application | Solo Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, Python, Django, SQL, JSX, Tailwind

- Built a social media type application that connects students to teachers as part of boot camp capstone.
- My goal for this project was to create a full-stack application with CRUD functionality.

Rare | Full-Stack Application | Group Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, JSX, CSS, Python, Django, SQL

- Built a 'Medium' like application as part of a group project.
- Gained experience collaborating with other developers building a full-stack application.

Education & Accreditations

Nashville Software School

04/2021 - 09/2021

- Focused on Full-Stack Development.
- Utilized Javascript, React, Python, Django, SQL, Postman

08/2018 - 05/2020

University of Tennessee, Knoxville

■ BA Economics